

**E-mail** Rizwan.techzoid111@gmail.com

Phone

+92 3555 923492

**Portfolio** 

https://rizuu-portfolio.netlify .app/@rizuu003

Github

https://github.com/AlyRizuu

#### **SKILLS**

**Custom Website** 



**Patient Care** 



**Team Work** 



#### **LANGUAGES**

English



Urdu



# RIZWAN ALI

# Front-End Developer

# ABOUT ME

I am Rizwan Ali from Pakistan, an experienced and professional Front-end Developer. I build quality, user-friendly, and responsive Custom websites. I am working as a Front-end Developer for years. I am extremely passionate about my work.

#### **EDUCATION**

- 2020-2022 | Public School and College, jutival Gilgit
   I have done intermediate in computer science with higher quality of education
- 2018-2020 | Public School and College, jutival Gilgit
  | have done matriculation in computer science
  | with higher quality of education

## **EXPERTIES**

I have Experties in:











## WORK EXPERIENCE

- 2020 to till date | Front-End Developer
   I have 3+ years of experience in website development. And I Am working as a front-end developer at Techzoid Pvt Ltd.
- 2021 to till date | Front-End Developer
  - 1 + Year of experience in freelancing on upwork as a Front-end developer.